Music
Lines soft on grass, sun warms my closed eyes
I hear life haunts coming through the skies
Maybe dreams bring the world alive that all feels new
All feels new
And I can sense joy that floats around me
Every shade of laughter will shine
Because somewhere I see a wagging tail appears
The magic is real right here
Ooh, whoa, softly, softly you run to me
So bright in this sunny dream
If I could have known that you're alive here
Just how I missed you
Then maybe I'd stay in this gentle world
But right here with you in my arms
Music
Softly, softly you run to me
So bright in this sunny dream
If I could have known that I can sense
Joy that floats around me
Every shade of laughter will shine
Because somewhere I see a wagging tail appears
The magic is real right here
Ooh, whoa, softly, softly you run to me
So bright in this sunny dream
If I could have known that you're alive here
Just how I missed you